44f5
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>James &#8211; TDP Fantasy Football Write-Ups</title>
	<atom:link href="/ff-writeup/index.php/author/admin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/ff-writeup/</link>
	<description>Earning his spot, as he always has.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 01:21:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Week 3</title>
		<link>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/26/week-3/</link>
		<comments>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/26/week-3/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 01:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ff-writeup/?p=70</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlenerds. The Browns won a game. Go ahead, rub your eyes in disbelief. You read that correctly. The Cleveland Browns. The worst team the modern NFL has ever seen. Won. A. Game. 19 games. Your team might get obliterated by the Buffalo Bills. Your team might lose the NFC Championship in heartbreaking fashion. &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/26/week-3/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Week 3"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ladies and gentlenerds.</p>
<p>The Browns won a game.</p>
<p>Go ahead, rub your eyes in disbelief. You read that correctly.</p>
<p>The Cleveland Browns. The worst team the modern NFL has ever seen. Won. A. Game.</p>
<p>19 games. Your team might get obliterated by the Buffalo Bills. Your team might lose the NFC Championship in heartbreaking fashion. Your team might be cursed with awful placekicking when it matters the most (or maybe that’s all just my team). But, in all likelihood, you’ll never see your team fail to win 19 consecutive games. But Browns fans did just that. And they deserve to enjoy that dub.</p>
<p>More important to you nerds, who aren’t Browns fans, is the manner in which they won that first game in two years. Backup quarterback, Baker Mayfield—the number one overall draft pick by the Browns—heralded as the hopeful savior of Cleveland, got his first real taste of NFL action, and my god, was it a good one. Baker marched down the field, repeatedly, to a tune of 17 for 23, and led the Browns in a heroic second half comeback to take the W from Sam Darnold’s New York Jets. Don’t know what’s in the rookie QBs water, but I want some of it.</p>
<div style="width: 100%; height: 0px; position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.250%;"><iframe style="width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute;" src="https://streamable.com/s/7u9pe/mpxqqv" width="100%" height="100%" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>I don’t know what’s in store for Baker. He was fantastic in college, and he was—in my pleb opinion—the best QB coming into the NFL this season. One game, no matter how excellent it was, is not nearly enough to crown him as “for real.”</p>
<p>That being said, the hype RV has officially left the parking lot. And we’re all aboard for the ride.</p>
<p>Is this where I’m supposed to say “Boomer Sooner?” I’m not good at this whole James thing.</p>
<p>With that, let’s recap this week’s fantasy matchups, starting with mine.</p>
<p><strong><u>The Best Friend Bowl</u></strong></p>
<p>Reece v. Dame 2. Last year’s week 3 marquee matchup, where Reece completely blew me out, 109.6 to 73.6. This year’s week 3 marquee matchup….where Reece completely blew me out, 116 to 82.6. Two years, two 30 point Ls. Reece got a <em>ton</em> of help from his new players, Sanders and Beckham, who combined for 30 points. Sanders had a 35 yard rushing touchdown, which completely deflated me, and Beckham turned around from a horribly mediocre performance against the Boys to thrash the Houston D. I’m blaming Ian; if Reece had Ajayi and Thielen still, I <em>totally</em> would’ve won. Or at least could have. But probably not. Not with how well Reece’s team as a whole performed. I roasted Reece at the draft saying he’d be 0-4 without Ingram. Turns out, I’m wrong. Again.</p>
<p>On the bright side—for me—McCaffrey is beyond <strong><em>legit</em></strong>. This is two weeks in a row where he puts up 20 points without a touchdown in either, which is nuts. One week of 100+ yards through the air, another of 180+ yards on the ground. Looks like the entire Panthers offense runs through McCaffrey, and once those tuddys start coming, you’re all absolutely fucked. The rest of my team may have underperformed—looking at you, Dan Bailey and the Vikings offense—but McCaffrey is looking to be a bona fide RB1. Sure am glad he’s in my starting lineup this week against Ian!</p>
<p><em>Wait,<strong> who’s </strong>on bye?</em></p>
<div style="width: 100%; height: 0px; position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.250%;"><iframe style="width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute;" src="https://streamable.com/s/za9ih/guosnu" width="100%" height="100%" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<div></div>
<p><strong><u>Fournette Who?</u></strong></p>
<p>Under no circumstances did I think Jaiden would be this good. He had a great team at the draft for sure, but Jaiden leading the league? It’d definitely be someone more experienced, like me, or Chris, or Thomas. However, dumbass Dame reveals himself again, as Jaiden is completely steamrolling everyone in the league, and we’re all powerless to stop it. Alvin Kamara got <em>twenty targets</em>, reeling in 15 for catches. Remember how just above I was getting off to CMC putting up 20 points without a TD? Kamara put up <em>26 </em>without a touchdown. I want off Mr. Tennessee’s Wild Ride, but I can absolutely see why Jaiden wouldn’t. Also, I think Crowell exceeding his entire last year’s point total just this week, which is absurd. And there was also that Vance McDonald play that got our favorite rapist another tuddy on the board. Who needs Fournette when everyone else is a superstar?</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Justin is not looking hot through 3 weeks. Sorry, bud. Michael Thomas is putting up league records—did you know that he has the most receptions through 3 games in NFL history?—but Justin’s RB corps is absolutely abysmal. 4.3 from Duke Johnson, who is his number 2—maybe 1—RB right now. You may need to make a trade, my friend. Tell ya what, I’ll give you Peyton Barber for Michael Thomas, who says no?</p>
<p><strong><u>Boomers vs. Sooners</u></strong></p>
<p>We have the Oklahoma Bowl here this week, as reigning champion Thomas Huerta takes on reigning title belt holder James Land. Based on this outcome matchup, James continues to be the reigning Chad from Oklahoma, while Thomas is very much the virgin. I take some of the blame; Thomas asked me how confident I was in Diggs/Murray this week, and I told him “100% would fire them both up with no regrets, wouldn’t be surprised to see each put up 25.” Well, I was wrong, and the Vikings sucked. 2/9 of Thomas’s offense went out the window along with the Vikings, and there was no salvaging that. Sorry about that, bud.</p>
<p>James, meanwhile, was the biggest beneficiary of the Saints/Falcons shootout today. 20 points? That’s nothing to Brees. 30? Still a joke. How about 40? That’s more up Breesus’s alley. Landry proving to be a low-end WR1 at worst—which James has given me much deserved shit for doubting—and the Kansas City offense showing that they’re done “running through one player” like they did last year. Hunt game/Hill game/Kelce game? Gone are those days. Now everyone feasts. All hail Pat Mahomes, our one true God.</p>
<p><strong><u>Battle of the Badgers</u></strong></p>
<p>0-2 waiver “champion” Tony Cudz takes on Mike “Mike” Fortman this week in the Badger Bowl. Tony’s probably wishing he didn’t drop Matt Ryan now, who would’ve catapulted his team into a victory this week. Tony’s RBs were not too bad this week; 12.7 points out of Morris—with a ton of upside if Breida is hurt—is looking good, and his receivers showed up as best they could. Tony’s starters were lacking in the tuddy department, which kept him from getting the dub this week. Slowly but surely he’s coming around, but Big Ton’ might need to make some moves to get a better RB at this rate. Ton of WR talent on the bench he can’t start, not a lot in the backfield.</p>
<p>Mike’s team, meanwhile, hasn’t lost a step without Mixon. Gio Bernard stepped in and did exactly what he needed to do; Alex Collins got the goal-line carries—which 11 of the 12 members of the league thought would happen—but Amari Cooper went back to being, well, Amari Cooper. Xavien Howard looks to be a legitimate top 5 corner, so I can’t say I’m surprised. Fins Up, baby. Mike’s looking up from here on out, sitting at 2-1 with Calvin Ridley on his bench and a team with no clear weakness.</p>
<p><strong><u>Upset Alert!</u></strong></p>
<p>Title is self-explanatory. #1 in points forced, one of the few undefeated teams left, facing an 0-2-and-also-almost-last-in-points-forced Oron, whoda thunk that Chris would fall now? Well, who thought the Bills would beat the Vikings? Nobody, that’s who.</p>
<p>Chris and Thomas both suffered from Vikings-itis this week, as the awful performance by Minnesota completely tanked his chances this week, too. 10 points from your QB is not going to get it done without a stellar performance from your skill players, and Chris, unfortunately, didn’t get that. Kareem Hunt put up 2 tuddys, but even that wasn’t enough to get him into the top RBs this week. Engram and Cole disappointed, relative to their expectations this week, and Fat Randy did Fat Randy things. Namely, not good things. Don’t worry bud, I took the Dan Bailey donut for you. Thank me later.</p>
<p>Oron, on the other hand, showed why he targeted the players that he did. Carlos Hyde’s usage has been out of this world, and he was bound to feast. Well, he did. Royce Freeman once again got goal line carries, showing everyone about how washed he is and how “pHiLiP lInDsAy Is GoNnA oWn ThAt BaCkFiElD.” I know Lindsay got ejected, but still, shut nerd. Fitzmagic went full Fitztragic <em>and back to Fitzmagic</em>, and with the loss of Jimmy G, I see Oron riding this bearded beauty until the wheels fall off. And they will. I just wonder how many wins Oron is going to rack up before then.</p>
<div style="width: 100%; height: 0px; position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.250%;"><iframe style="width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute;" src="https://streamable.com/s/kgr76/lvxnyl" width="100%" height="100%" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<div></div>
<p><strong><u>Super Sharma</u></strong></p>
<p>Can Sidd be stopped? For the third week, Sidd is in the upper echelon in scoring, and this time he actually got the benefit of the GOAT, Pat Mahomes. Speaking of who, I’m going to spend the next paragraph expressing my inner feelings for Pat Mahomes.</p>
<p>Pat Mahomes can slang it like a motherfucker. Pat Mahomes holds the NCAA record in single-game passing yards, but he also holds the NFL record for biggest balls. I don’t know how Pat Mahomes can throw the ball as well as he does with his balls being that gigantic. Did you see that rollout TD? If I could marry a touchdown pass, that would be the one I pick. Three games, 13 tuddys, no picks. Watson last year was just the appetizer; Pat Mahomes is the main entrée. Sidd doesn’t need receivers. Sidd has God.</p>
<p>Oh yeah, and then there’s Ian. Ian’s team has been great all season (minus last week), but this week he unfortunately ran into the Sidd buzzsaw. Ian totaled the 4<sup>th</sup> highest scoring output this week, led by the thiccest boi in the league, Saquon Barkley. Will Fuller might actually be the real deal; Adam Thielen did Adam Thielen things (namely, feast); and Jordan Howard’s usage is only somewhat concerning! Don’t be surprised if we see Ian in the playoffs. His team is legit.</p>
<p>With all of these words out of the way, let’s get into the good stuff: our Weekly Superlatives.</p>
<p><strong>Top Team</strong></p>
<p>Sidd, with the world’s greatest quarterback at the helm, led his team to an astoundi-….</p>
<p>…wait, Sidd didn’t get Top Player? Who did?</p>
<p><em>Oh dear god.</em></p>
<p>Jaiden, with a whopping 140.9, takes the top team title this week. Not a single hole on Jaiden’s team this week—every single player but Njoku put up double digits—including a perfectly normal 26.5 from Kamara and 24 from the league’s #1 alleged rapist. Round and round the schedule goes, who can stop Jaiden? Hell if I know.</p>
<p><strong>Highest Scoring Loser</strong></p>
<p>Goes to the one and only Ian Kwan. Ian had a rough week last week, but rebounded in a fantastic way, managing to have the 4<sup>th</sup> most points forced this week! Unfortunately, the luck of the draw had him matched up against Sidd, and not even the 4<sup>th</sup> most was enough to save his record. This blurb is usually used to roast owners for bad decisions, but there was nothing that Ian could do this week. Things just weren’t meant to be. Much like me having thighs like Saquon.</p>
<p><strong>Lowest Scoring Winner</strong></p>
<p>Mr. Fortman. Wisconsin’s favorite son. Sorry Tony, you lost that title this week along with the game. Mike’s 92 would’ve only beaten 4 teams this week, and he got lucky that he was matched up against one of ‘em. Amari is, once again, a total bum. Chris Thompson got game-scripted out. Doesn’t matter; still won. Please file all complaints to the number 2 in the win column.</p>
<p><strong>Bottom of the Barrel</strong></p>
<p>Justin friggin’ Katz. So at the end of the draft, we all unanimously agreed that Tony had the worst team, right?</p>
<p>Well, we were wrong. Sorry bud. Tony has 3 elite receivers and no RBs; you, my friend, only have two, and even worse RBs. Justin, thanks to Shady’s ribs, had to start a backfield combination of Duke Johnson and LeGarrette Blount. If you gagged reading that, I understand completely. Brady also completely fell off the wagon this week, leaving our pal Justin in last place, and falling to 0-3. I hope you turn it around, my friend. Fantasy’s more fun when you do.</p>
<p><strong>Top Player</strong></p>
<p>I’m going to give this a two-fer. Top player based on score this week goes to James, who started Drew Brees and won a sweet $5 for it. Remember, kids, this week’s was about “highest scoring QB.” Really, top player in my mind is “player who most surpassed expectations,” which would go to Mike and his benched Calvin Ridley. Holy hell. WR3 on the depth chart and 3 tuddys. If he was on FAAB, someone (re: Sidd) would be spending a ton of money on him right about now.</p>
<p><strong>Worst Start</strong></p>
<p>Oh no, it’s me, isn’t it?</p>
<p>Oh wait, thanks Oron. Oron with the Chargers D/ST going against the Rams. -4 from a defense is very much in “not good territory,” especially when almost anyone could tell you that the Rams were going to roll them.</p>
<p>Honorable mention to me for spending $6 on a kicker that didn’t even attempt an XP, let alone a FG. Fuck the Vikings. Why couldn’t I have just been born a shitty Pats fan?</p>
<p><strong>Worst Bench</strong></p>
<p>Reece, you knew it was coming. Reece DM’d me before the game talking about how he was going to start Derrick Henry over both Adrian Peterson and Buck Allen, because of some stupid stuff about “zone blocking” and “Alabama.” Well, ya dingus, you benched both RBs who tripled—even quadrupled for AD!&#8211;his output. Especially bad given how hard we all grilled you for spending on Buck Allen. For you to be proven right and not reap the rewards, you gotta get this award.</p>
<p><strong>Weekly Challenge Winner</strong></p>
<p>Who came up with this shit? The commish wins again? I call rigged. Crooked James stealing our money right from under our noses.</p>
<p>James wins $5 and the aptly named “Uncle Rico Award” for Drew Brees channeling his inner Patrick Mahomes to will the Saints to an OT victory. Next week, we have the Samaje “Adrian ‘All Day’ Peterson” Perine award: $5 goes to whoever starts the RB with the most yards from scrimmage.</p>
<p>Note, I said yards. Your mediocre pass-catching RB in a stupid John Harbaugh committee that oppresses my high school boi Alex Collins can get 4 tuddys all he wants; we’re caring about yardage this week. Fingers crossed it’s Barber. Or Williams. Whichever one I decide to start. I need anything.</p>
<p>3 weeks in the books, boys. Now we can start to see who the good teams are and who might not be. Still though, the season’s young. No need to overreact. No need to sell your players for trash (unless it’s to me). Everything’s still open season.</p>
<p>Thanks for reading. I’ll be back in a couple weeks to write another 2,500 word essay on Fantasy Football.</p>

2e97
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/26/week-3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Week 2</title>
		<link>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/19/week-2/</link>
		<comments>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/19/week-2/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 02:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ff-writeup/?p=58</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[You know, I’ve been thinking a lot about this week’s football events, and I’ve come to a very profound conclusion. Football is a cruel sport. Now, I’m not talking about cruel as in the hits that players take on a weekly basis, the long term damage that can be sustained  from the game, or even &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/19/week-2/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Week 2"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You know, I’ve been thinking a lot about this week’s football events, and I’ve come to a very profound conclusion. Football is a cruel sport. Now, I’m not talking about cruel as in the hits that players take on a weekly basis, the long term damage that can be sustained  from the game, or even the insults that players hurl at each other. No, I’m speaking of cruelty to the most important participant in the football experience: the football fan.</p>
<p>Football fans don’t expect much. All we want is to cheer on our own team, or, failing that, to cheer on a worthy underdog, and for a dramatic story to turn into an exciting ending. In the NFL, there are 32 teams. This means that every year, fans of 31 teams feel like the NFL is cruel and unjust. “Why can’t my team win a Super Bowl?” they wonder, as their team loses a game which inevitably ends their run at a championship, whether that be in week 10 or in February. Now, never mind the fact that every team has about as good of a shot as the others to win every year, and can rebuild through the draft, fire and replace coaches who suck, and usually end up with dramatically fluctuating records from season to season. This was our year, dammit, and we were due! Why are the football gods so unjust to MY team?</p>
<div style="width: 525px;" class="wp-video"><video class="wp-video-shortcode" id="video-58-4" width="525" height="295" preload="metadata" controls="controls"><source type="video/mp4" src="https://media.giphy.com/media/lorP90kfUe374yK7T3/giphy.mp4?_=4" /><a href="https://media.giphy.com/media/lorP90kfUe374yK7T3/giphy.mp4">https://media.giphy.com/media/lorP90kfUe374yK7T3/giphy.mp4</a></video></div>
<p>College football is cruel. So cruel, that when you get one or two losses, it totally eliminates you from championship contention. It’s cutthroat, take no prisoners football, with every game a moment to say something about whether you’re good enough or not. Sometimes you win, but sometimes you just get your doors blown off by a real contender. Take Alabama vs. Ole Miss this past weekend. Ole Miss, on the very first play, aired it out to D.K Matcalf for a 75 yard touchdown score and gave their fans, and the fans around the world, a little sliver of hope that Alabama was vulnerable. The final score of this game was 62-7 in favor of the Crimson Tide. No, world, Alabama is not vulnerable and is in fact very good, as per usual. Cruelty.</p>
<p>But sometimes, even the small things seem cruel. The Browns were everyone’s favorite punching bag last year, and the year before, and the year before, and… well god dammit, everybody wants to see them succeed this year. Josh Gordon is everyone’s favorite comeback player – a guy who is trying to reestablish himself as a dominant receiver after a few years absence from the NFL due to his problems with addiction. The ultimate Cinderella story would be the Browns winning again, with Josh Gordon leading the charge as their star receiver. Sadly, neither of those things look promising. The Cleveland Browns have still not won a football game since 2016 (ties do NOT count as wins), and after Gordon was late to a practice this past week, have decided to trade the receiver to the New England Patriots, of all teams, for a measly fifth round pick. The Browns remind us once again that they are in football hell, and unless proven otherwise, that is where we believe they will stay.</p>
<p>Yes, football is often very cruel, and the things that you wish would happen often do not. However, when those things do happen – when the stars align, the miracle play is made, the underdog wins the Super Bowl in dramatic fashion – it only makes them that much more special.</p>
<p><strong>Top Player</strong></p>
<p>This week, Chris takes the high score with 140 points! Chris’s team had a fantastic week, as all of his first seven players ended up with double digit scores! Kirk Cousins put up a 33 point day in an overtime game vs Green Bay. Hunt and Cook were solid double-digit backs. Mike Evans was a beneficiary of another week of Fitzmagic, JuJu was the top Steelers receiver, and Cooks balled out vs a hapless Arizona team. Even Evan Engram earned enough points in an otherwise uninspired Giants offensive effort to put him above the fifteen point mark. The only dull spots were the Jaguars D vs. New England and an injured kicker. Hats off to Chris this week!</p>
<p><strong>Highest Scoring Loser</strong></p>
<p>The outcome of this game was exciting, and what a close game it was. With Monday Night Football remaining, the only player left to play was Cody Parkey, the kicker for the Chicago Bears, vs the Seattle Seahawks. All that needed to happen was for the Seahawks to hold the kicker to 4 or fewer points, and Sidd would squeak out the victory. Alas, it was not meant to be for poor Sidd, as Cody Parkey kicked the game-winning extra point early in the fourth quarter, with a follow up kick later on, after the pick six. Games this close always leave the loser questioning every decision ever made in fantasy football. Man, if only I had started any of my bench wideouts over Robby Anderson, or had swapped this quarterback for that quarterback. More on that later on.</p>
<p><strong>Lowest Scoring Winner</strong></p>
<div style="width: 525px;" class="wp-video"><video class="wp-video-shortcode" id="video-58-5" width="525" height="295" preload="metadata" controls="controls"><source type="video/mp4" src="https://media.giphy.com/media/MTsBCHIQrzEddYGKpF/giphy.mp4?_=5" /><a href="https://media.giphy.com/media/MTsBCHIQrzEddYGKpF/giphy.mp4">https://media.giphy.com/media/MTsBCHIQrzEddYGKpF/giphy.mp4</a></video></div>
<p>Going back to that Monday Night Football game, I was sure that I was cooked, after Seattle scored in the fourth quarter to make it 17-10. At that point, I was at a two point deficit to Justin, and I figured the difference would only grow from there. I started working on the main section of the write-up, talking about how football could be so cruel, and so on. By the way, in case you haven’t been paying attention, I’m not good at losing. I can be very competitive, even for the most trivial things. So when Prince Amukamara knew what play Russell Wilson was going to run out of the empty set, and stepped in front of his pass, and housed it, I got reaaaaally excited. Even though it’s just one fantasy football game, and even though I didn’t really care whether the Bears or the Seahawks actually won that game, I went nuts. I would have lost to six of the teams this week.</p>
<p><strong>Bottom of the Barrel</strong></p>
<p>The thing that surprises me most about Mike’s team this week is how low Aaron Rodgers’s score is. Kirk Cousins scored over 30, and these two played in the same overtime game! Yeah, I guess he was nursing his knee injury that he got <em>carted off the field for</em> last week, but his yardage total isn’t that much lower than last week’s. He did only have one passing touchdown though, as opposed to Cousins with four. That’ll do it. The other thing was how well Jacksonville did in shutting down Rob Gronkowski. I remember watching that game, and Tony (Romo) mentioning how well Jacksonville was defending Gronk, and how many different ways they were doing it. I think at one point they sent a safety over to cover him near the sideline, and dropped their linebacker, Myles Jack, back into the safety position in cover 1, which was nuts to me. Anyways, Mike will look to bounce back this week vs. Tony (Cudz).</p>
<p><strong>Top Player</strong></p>
<p>There were a LOT of quarterback points in the KC vs. Pittsburgh shootout. Even though Mahomes had more touchdowns, Big Ben ended up with more points, on account of his rushing score. Remember kids: rushing is more important than passing. At least for your quarterback.</p>
<p><strong>Worst Start</strong></p>
<div style="width: 525px;" class="wp-video"><video class="wp-video-shortcode" id="video-58-6" width="525" height="295" preload="metadata" controls="controls"><source type="video/mp4" src="https://media.giphy.com/media/3iCp9N7etV5BbzSjaH/giphy.mp4?_=6" /><a href="https://media.giphy.com/media/3iCp9N7etV5BbzSjaH/giphy.mp4">https://media.giphy.com/media/3iCp9N7etV5BbzSjaH/giphy.mp4</a></video></div>
<p>We had a pair of bad defenses this week. Cincinnati put the hurt on the Ravens on Thursday Night Football, after A.J. Green’s explosive, Will-Fuller-like performance in the first half and no redeeming points thereafter (not even a single sack). On the other side of this matchup, the Panthers were unable to handle Steve Sarkisian’s wit, and allowed 31 points to the Falcons. At least they got a pick out of Matt Ryan!</p>
<p><strong>Worst Bench</strong></p>
<p>Sidd, you knew it was coming. Well, here it is. Patrick Mahomes, with all the weapons he has in that Kansas City offense, looks like the young prodigy everybody said he would be. And when you sit him down on the day he throws for SIX TOUCHDOWNS vs. the Pittsburgh Steelers, you have made a big mistake. Now, I know what you’re going to say to me. “But James, Deshaun Watson didn’t have a bad day! It’s tough to make a decision between Mahomes and Watson! I’m a nerd!” Well, I don’t know why you brought up that last thing, but shut for a minute and let me share my opinion. I think it’s safe to say that Patrick Mahomes had a better performance in week one than Deshaun Watson. Patrick Mahomes threw for 256 yards and 4* touchdowns vs the LA Chargers in week one (*at least one of those TDs should be classified as a handoff, but whatever). Deshaun Watson threw for about a buck seventy-five, with a touchdown, an interception, and a lost fumble. At the beginning of the season, I would say that Watson and Mahomes have had about the same experience in the NFL. Maybe give Watson a little more experience in actual games, but they’re both in their second year. Patrick Mahomes has two major weapons in Tyreek Hill and Travis Kelce, while Houston&#8217;s weapons include Hopkins, and sometimes Fuller. Plus, Patrick Mahomes is just really, really talented, with a cannon arm and a quick release. So yeah, I probably would have gone with Mahomes. And you will too, next week.</p>
<p><strong>Weekly Challenge Winner</strong></p>
<p>This week’s weekly challenge was the biggest drop off from week one to week two. This includes all bench players. And, well, I won! I dropped off from 180.6 down to 136.3 this week, a difference of 44.3. Thomas was second with a difference of 32.4. Reece rose the most, from 123.9 to 166.8 (+42.9).</p>
<p>Damian has graciously been voluntold to do the write-up for this coming week. Please, give him the same respect that you give me. Because otherwise he won’t do it again, and I need a break every once in a while.</p>

336e
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/19/week-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Week 1</title>
		<link>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/12/week-1/</link>
		<comments>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/12/week-1/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ff-writeup/?p=47</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Gentlemen and… gentlemen, week one of the 2018 NFL season (and our fantasy football season) has come to a close. And man, am I glad that NFL football is back. It was an entertaining week one, that’s for sure. This week had just about everything, from low-scoring defensive slugfests, to high-octane shootouts, to blowouts, to &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/12/week-1/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Week 1"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gentlemen and… gentlemen, week one of the 2018 NFL season (and our fantasy football season) has come to a close. And man, am I glad that NFL football is back. It was an entertaining week one, that’s for sure. This week had just about everything, from low-scoring defensive slugfests, to high-octane shootouts, to blowouts, to ties, to rain delays, and to top it all off, another fucking Aaron Rodgers miracle game. So I think for the writeup this week, I’m just gonna talk about the things that excited me about this opening weekend of football played at the very highest of levels, unless you’re watching the Dallas Cowboys offense.</p>
<p>First off, we had that Thursday night game, Eagles v. Falcons. I was mainly just watching this game to pass time waiting for the new Spider-Man game to finally be released at 11:00 pm that evening. (Sidebar, that Spider-Man game is fucking fantastic and if you are even a slight fan of the wall-crawler you should play it, it’s so fun and the story is amazing.) The game kicked off late after a 45 minute rain delay, and the story of that game was how the Falcons seemed to drive the ball decently, but when they got down into the red zone they could just not do a damn thing. Early on they went for it on fourth and goal from the one and got no points. I remember being confused (and somewhat relieved) that Julio came out of the game in the red zone on that first drive. I also loved making fun of Reece for his comments on Ajayi until he actually became the workhorse in the second half.</p>
<div style="width: 525px;" class="wp-video"><video class="wp-video-shortcode" id="video-47-10" width="525" height="295" preload="metadata" controls="controls"><source type="video/mp4" src="https://media.giphy.com/media/SJCmvBZlxsMg8A7J28/giphy.mp4?_=10" /><a href="https://media.giphy.com/media/SJCmvBZlxsMg8A7J28/giphy.mp4">https://media.giphy.com/media/SJCmvBZlxsMg8A7J28/giphy.mp4</a></video></div>
<p>Sunday morning, I mostly watched the Browns face off vs. their division rivals, the Pittsburgh Steelers. I was especially looking forward to this game, not only because the Browns were rumored to be much improved from last year, but also because I got to watch my new RB, the cancer survivor who shares my name, James Conner. And man was he effective. I don’t even remember the name of the running back that I paid $83 dollars for in the draft. Anyways, the Steelers were up 21-7 in the fourth and I thought that the Browns were just about finished, and then Miles Garrett happened. Suddenly, a forced fumble and a Hyde touchdown later, the Browns had a chance. Following that, a late drive and a touchdown from Gordon sent the game to OT. Both teams had opportunities to checkmate, but blunders on both sides forced the two sides to agree to a draw. Er, you know what I mean. A missed field goal by Chris Boswell of the Steelers, and a blocked field goal on the Browns’ game winning attempt by T.J. Watt, eventually led us to a 21-21 draw. So the Browns no longer have a losing streak!</p>
<p>In the afternoon, I watched the Cowboys struggle to do fucking anything vs. the Panthers. Dak and the boys couldn’t get it going on offense. Zeke was mostly stacked up at the line, which is not something I’m used to seeing from our line – they usually can move guys and zone block pretty well. It’s probably the absence of Frederick that’s hurting us there, but Connor Williams, our new left guard that we drafted and were excited about, was struggling as well. In the passing game, we were clueless. There were a couple of third down conversions to Beasley, but that’s about it. No Dez, no Witten, no offense. Dak was never really comfortable, and was missing guys low a few times. But hey, the defense was pretty good. I think we’ll still win some games, but there’s not a lot of talent there on offense for the Cowboys to do what we’ve come to expect from them.</p>
<div style="width: 525px;" class="wp-video"><video class="wp-video-shortcode" id="video-47-11" width="525" height="295" preload="metadata" controls="controls"><source type="video/mp4" src="https://media.giphy.com/media/4NaKWSUHK9sBqsTJX4/giphy.mp4?_=11" /><a href="https://media.giphy.com/media/4NaKWSUHK9sBqsTJX4/giphy.mp4">https://media.giphy.com/media/4NaKWSUHK9sBqsTJX4/giphy.mp4</a></video></div>
<p>I heard smatterings about some other games during the day. Ryan Fitzmagic lit the Saints up in the best passing day of his career, which was probably the biggest surprise of the day. The Bills fucking suck – who would have thought that starting a guy who threw 5 picks in a half wouldn’t turn out well? Adrian Peterson is back, or the Cardinals are terrible – probably a little of columns A &amp; B on that one. The Titans and the Dolphins played the longest game in the history of football, because they got delayed for three hours. Finally, the Sunday night game. I watched the second quarter of this game, and assumed that the Bears were going to win, based on a few key details that I uncovered while watching the broadcast.</p>
<ul>
<li>The Bears had a 17-0 lead going into the half.</li>
<li>Khalil Mack was having a monster day, being directly involved in two turnovers</li>
<li>Aaron Rodgers was already carted off with a knee injury.</li>
<li>Deshone Kiser was the backup QB.</li>
</ul>
<p>Based on these details, I figured that 2 + 2 = 4 and went back to playing Spider-Man. Turns out, 2 + 2 = fucking 9000 because that’s A-Rod’s power level. Of course he came back, and of course the Packers came back to win at home, because that’s what they do. Hats off to the guy, he’s a miracle-worker.</p>
<p>And now, the week’s superlatives.</p>
<p><strong>Top Team</strong>: Hello everyone. It feels weird to write a blurb about myself for the top team, because I don’t think it ever happened last year. But I hit on just about every player on my team. At QB, Drew Brees was predictably high-scoring vs the Bucs, with the second highest fantasy numbers behind Ryan Fitzmagic. After losing Bell, I quickly and quietly scooped up James Conner off FAAB, and then he put up 30 points. Dion Lewis, after a slow start, took over the Titans backfield after the rain delay and scored a nice 17 points. All of my receivers had solid outings – Fitzgerald got 10 points in a losing effort, Landry found some nice catches late vs the Steelers, and Crabtree got a touchdown vs. the Bills. The Titans D was good vs. the Dolphins, with a couple of picks. The only two players who didn’t really pan out were Kelce and Chris Boswell, who missed a game winning FG, but I can live with that. All-in-all, good week one.</p>
<p><strong>Highest-Scoring Loser: </strong>So I wrote two possible blurbs for this category, because at the time of writing the rest of the writeup yesterday (Monday evening), the two leading candidates were Jaiden and Anthony. Turns out, neither of them ended up being the highest scoring loser. In fact, one of them ended up winning over the actual highest-scoring loser, Thomas! The Jaiden v. Thomas game was won by the slimmest of margins, at the last minute. Watch below – if you look closely, you can pinpoint the second when Thomas’s heart rips in half.</p>
<div style="width: 525px;" class="wp-video"><video class="wp-video-shortcode" id="video-47-12" width="525" height="295" preload="metadata" controls="controls"><source type="video/mp4" src="https://media.giphy.com/media/g0stiPJNCMCycsq7kj/giphy.mp4?_=12" /><a href="https://media.giphy.com/media/g0stiPJNCMCycsq7kj/giphy.mp4">https://media.giphy.com/media/g0stiPJNCMCycsq7kj/giphy.mp4</a></video></div>
<p>Ouch. A pick six with two minutes left in the Rams/Raiders game to bring the Rams D to 15 points, which edged Thomas 129-128. I gotta say, that’s heartbreaking. Even though Thomas does have the highest-scoring player (Tyreek Hill, below), he couldn’t quite get the win over Jaiden. Ah well, it’s only one week!</p>
<p><strong>Lowest-Scoring Win: </strong>Sidd’s lowest scoring win this week honestly wasn’t that low-scoring. 114.1 is a solid score, even in half-PPR. 20 point games from both of his running backs was honestly expected. Watson had an awful day and still put up 11 points, which is better than a couple other starting QBs around the league. He also got loads of points out of his D and kicker. Sidd would have beat every other loser except Thomas.</p>
<p><strong>Bottom of the Barrel:</strong></p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FZUcpVmEHuk" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p>Hey, Sidd. Didn’t you run all of our draft teams through a program to see who performed the best? Who was number one? Was it this week’s dumpster fire of a team, owned by last year’s second place finisher, Damian Larson? It was? Wow, that’s surprising! I guess their algorithms weren’t very good. Maybe if they added IBM’s Fantasy Insights With Watson<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/11/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> it would have been more accurate.</p>
<p>But man, talk about rotten luck. The Cardinals on offense struggled to get anything going, which limited David Johnson. Christian McCaffrey fumbled on his first drive where he might have scored – an 8 point swing right there. Chris Hogan turned out to not be Brady’s number one WR target. Jimmy Graham was irrelevant. Jamaal Williams averaged like three yards a carry. And good god, that Saints D (more discussion below). There were some bright spots, though. Rivers was the third best QB on the day, with 29 points. Golden Tate had a solid outing Monday evening vs. the Jets. And Vinatieri looks to be a kicker you can trust again, now that Luck is on his side.</p>
<p><strong>Top Player: </strong></p>
<div style="width: 525px;" class="wp-video"><video class="wp-video-shortcode" id="video-47-13" width="525" height="295" preload="metadata" controls="controls"><source type="video/mp4" src="https://media.giphy.com/media/1lCEVp6AaGAmVzI9PH/giphy.mp4?_=13" /><a href="https://media.giphy.com/media/1lCEVp6AaGAmVzI9PH/giphy.mp4">https://media.giphy.com/media/1lCEVp6AaGAmVzI9PH/giphy.mp4</a></video></div>
<p>Tyreek Hill is fast. Mahomes and Hill hooked up once for a huge bomb in the preseason, which gave you an idea of just how deadly that combination could be. I think defenses are going to have a real problem with Hill this year. I was worried a little about Mahomes (as I am with all new quarterbacks). I thought he might be too raw this year, and throw a lot of picks. He still may. But Hill is certainly a proven weapon. I hope that after this game, defenses start to overprepare for Hill and forget about the other threat, Travis Kelce. Please.</p>
<p><strong>Worst Start: </strong>Hey, it is roast Damian day! Whenever you start a team defense that scores a -9, you get roasted, no matter how much everyone thought the Bucs would suck going into this game. Damian was on the wrong end of Fitzmagic this time. So what do we think of the Saints D going forward? Are they worth trying again, or are they going to give up big yardage and over five touchdowns every game going forward? It’s hard to say, but I have a general rule of not looking at defenses that post negative scores until proven otherwise.</p>
<p><strong>Worst Bench: </strong>I’d say the combination of Mahomes + Kittle for Sidd this week would be the worst benching decisions. It didn’t really end up mattering for Sidd, but both of them would have been massive upgrades to the Watson and Mike Gesicki combo that he started. Ekeler would have been an upgrade over Lynch too, surprisingly, but I don’t fault him for not starting Ekeler.</p>
<p><strong>Weekly Challenge: </strong>After tallying up the numbers, the highest score for starters + bench goes to Sidd! Way to earn that $5. Honestly, it wasn’t even close – his 190.5 was a good ten points above the next best player, me. Take your damn money.</p>

358e
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/09/12/week-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Preseason Discussion</title>
		<link>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/08/12/preseason/</link>
		<comments>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/08/12/preseason/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 19:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ff-writeup/?p=1</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I’m baaaaaaaaaaack&#8230; I’m gonna be bored all day in the airport today, so I figured I’d take some time and write the first write up of the 2018 fantasy football season! My head is a mishmash of preseason week one right now. At time of writing there’s still four teams yet to play, and one &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/08/12/preseason/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Preseason Discussion"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-full wp-image-39" src="/ff-writeup/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/ad_imbaaack.jpg" alt="" width="380" height="396" srcset="/ff-writeup/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/ad_imbaaack.jpg 380w, /ff-writeup/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/ad_imbaaack-288x300.jpg 288w" sizes="(max-width: 380px) 100vw, 380px" /></p>
<p>I’m baaaaaaaaaaack&#8230;</p>
<p>I’m gonna be bored all day in the airport today, so I figured I’d take some time and write the first write up of the 2018 fantasy football season! My head is a mishmash of preseason week one right now. At time of writing there’s still four teams yet to play, and one first round QB left to make his NFL debut. But I’d like to take the time to talk about the other four, and fill in Mr. Rosen when he plays later tonight (after I’ve departed from Albuquerque and arrived back in the good ol’ Dee Eff Dub). And then I’ll fill in some talk about league info, draft details, and tell you about YOUR chance to slot in your very own write up at some point this season.</p>
<p>With that being said, let’s talk QBs. I’ll go in order of preseason debut, so that means we’re going to start with the Heisman trophy winner. Er, the first one. Lamar Jackson.</p>
<p>Lamar Jackson has the advantage (or disadvantage?) of already playing two preseason games. I got to see a little bit of the Bears Ravens game on the way home from the TDP fun event last week, and I’ve seen the highlights from the game this week vs the Rams. Lamar Jackson gets a lot of Michael Vick comparisons, and I think that’s more what people want him to be rather than what he is right now. Of the four quarterbacks that I’ve seen so far, I actually think he needs the most work. Yes, that includes Josh Allen. LJ’s first instinct is to scramble a lot of the time, and  while that worked well at Louisville, NFL defenses aren’t going to let him get away with that most of the time. Maybe sometimes &#8211; he did have a nice rushing TD vs the Rams. But until the young QB proves that he can beat you deep, and do it consistently, the formula for defending Lamar Jackson becomes very simple. Clog up the running lanes and force him to try. I don’t think Lamar Jackson sees meaningful playing time until he cleans this up, with two experienced QBs in front of him.</p>
<p>Now, let’s move on to the Heisman trophy winner. Er, the second one. Baker Mayfield.</p>
<figure id="attachment_43" style="width: 320px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-43 size-full" title="(Callaway made a nice catch too)" src="/ff-writeup/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/baker.gif" alt="" width="320" height="180" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">It&#8217;s only preseason, and Baker&#8217;s already throwing like he&#8217;s in a divisional playoff game.</figcaption></figure>
<p>You guys are going to think I’m a dirty fucking homer, and you’re right. But I think Baker had the best rookie debut out of the five, and justified his first overall pick status. Also, I’ve kinda changed my mind about his ability to start in the NFL right now &#8211; I think he could play, and win games with the Browns. He won’t, because Tyrod Taylor is there and looks good too, but he could. He looks experienced already &#8211; the pace of the preseason NFL Giants defense did not affect his ability to tear it up and score two excellent TDs. His stats from that game are ok, but also a bit misleading. He went 11 of 20 for 212 yards and 2 TDs, but that includes a few drops from Antonio Callaway early on, and some  pressured throwaway decisions that were the right decisions. That was one thing that worried me about Baker coming out of college &#8211; he seemed to hold onto the ball too long, and would get into some bad situations because of it. He seems to have corrected that from his game, which is a nice step forward. But the positives are awesome. Baker converted about three third and longs, one of which was a circus throw off his back foot to Callaway, making a toe tap catch on the sideline. Baker avoids pressure well and goes through his reads with confidence, which is something he did exceptionally well in his last season at OU, so I’m not surprised it’s continuing here. He’s also got top notch ball placement, which was on display when he threw that slant to Callaway for a 50 yard TD on blanket coverage. I could go on, but this paragraph is huge already and you guys are probably tired of reading this love fest. So let’s move on.</p>
<figure id="attachment_42" style="width: 320px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-42 size-full" title="WEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE" src="/ff-writeup/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/allen.gif" alt="" width="320" height="180" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">That thing does not obey the laws of physics at all!</figcaption></figure>
<p>Josh Allen’s Bills debut was not aired on NFL network, so I had to watch highlights on YouTube. Josh Allen is such a crazy prospect that I don’t know what to think of him. He looks like a superhero who just figured out that he has super strength, and doesn’t quite know how to control it yet. Dude can throw the ball like 80 fucking yards in the air, and it doesn’t even look like he’s trying. The ball leaves his hand and flies like it was shot out of a cannon. It’s nuts. On the other hand, his accuracy is hit and miss. Sometimes he puts it right on the money, but sometimes he overthrows his receiver by five yards (after his receiver has already run like 60 yards holy shit). His footwork looks pretty crazy too. He’s so raw, which is why I was so confused when the Bills drafted him over Josh Rosen. The Bills are starting Nathan Peterman, who admittedly looked better than his 5 int half of football last season. However, between Josh Allen and Josh Rosen, I would have thought that Rosen would be the ideal choice, as he would be more prepared to start week one. The Bills confuse me. Anyways, not much has really changed with Allen since his pre-draft assessment. If he gets an NFL start this season, he’ll be fun to watch, for one reason or another.</p>
<p>And then there’s Sam Darnold. For me, I think Darnold was the second best QB, but didn’t really show much in the Jets preseason game. Darnold has a lot of traits which make him an attractive rookie QB. He has great poise in the pocket, and has above average accuracy among the rookie QBs. Here’s my problem with Darnold so far &#8211; check his stat line. Darnold completed 13 of 18 passes for 96 yards and one touchdown. That’s a 72% completion rate, which is excellent. However, he’s just at about 5.3 yards per attempt, which is low. For reference, that’s a lower number than the season stats for all of the 32 “qualified” (&gt;14 attempts per game played) QBs. Lowest is Joe Flacco with 5.72. Going back and watching the tape, about half of Darnold’s completed passes are swing passes out of the backfield. He had three completed passes over 10 yards. One was a pass to a wide open receiver. One was his touchdown pass, which was a great pass to the corner of the endzone. And one was a 3rd and 11 conversion, which was his best pass of the day, in my opinion. The rest was dink and dunk. I don’t know if it was a product of the Jets playcalling, or how the Falcons D was playing, or what, but I don’t feel like Darnold was asked to do anything really difficult yet. I would like to see more from the young QB before anointing him the starter.</p>
<p>I&#8217;m adding these Josh Rosen comments on Sunday night, after watching his preseason debut yesterday. It&#8217;s hard for me to slot him in somewhere because he was getting no help at all from his supporting cast, specifically his offensive line. He only played for a quarter, and that whole time he was either running for his life or crouching down to pick up low snaps.</p>
<p>Now that my random football thought of the week is over and done with, let’s talk about the league itself. This year, the league has undergone a few changes from last year. We’re trying out a few different rules, after some debate and discussion at Pluckers a couple of weeks ago. I’m going to list the most notable changes below:</p>
<p>First off, we’re switching to 0.5 PPR this year, which was the least controversial of the changes. With this scoring system in effect, the value of pass catching rbs and receivers who catch a lot of passes for short yardage increase, so basically that means you should spend $100 on Jarvis Landry.</p>
<p>Secondly, we’re doing an auction draft this year, which should be kind of crazy but also pretty fun. Grab your Beer sheets and start figuring out your favorite players, because everybody can get anybody for the right price this year. Budget is $200.</p>
<p>Third, we’re adding keeper rules, which will mostly take effect next year. Start looking for that draft steal worth a first rounder that you can get for $5 and keep for $20. Only one keeper allowed, and you can only keep for one year.</p>
<p>And finally, free agency is different this year. We’ll be utilizing FAAB (that’s Free Agency Acquisition Budget, for the acronymically challenged) with a budget of $100. Bids currently resolve every day at 11 AM with the exception of Tuesday. Tiebreakers are by reverse order of standing, and I don&#8217;t think that’s something I can alter.</p>
<p>Next order of business is to introduce all of the teams and their GMs. In reverse order of last year’s standings, here are the teams.</p>
<p>Taking over Harrison’s spot in the league is Chris Young. Also known as the only guy who would talk fantasy football with us last year who wasn’t in our league. Chris will certainly be a force in the upcoming season. I’m excited to see what he can do in our league, although I’m not excited about having another UF alum to constantly bring up 2008 all the time (looking at you, Damian).</p>
<p>Replacing Warren will be Oron Hazi. I don’t know as much about the fantasy basketball league, but I do know that Oron played in it. We’re happy to have him with us in football this year &#8211; it will be a nice change of pace from listening to Warren talk about his algorithms and how he “read the case” all year. If Oron applies the same levels of determination to FF that he did to DnB then his team will be successful.</p>
<p>Returning teams:</p>
<ul>
<li>Mike Fortman &#8211; After a dismal start, Mike bounced back to win a few, but could not overcome his initial struggles in order to contend for playoffs. Mike hopes to rebound this season.</li>
<li>Justin Katz &#8211; An early season 40 from Kareem Hunt looked promising for Justin, but his hopes fell flat down the stretch. Could this be the year that Justin climbs to the top of the ranks?</li>
<li>Ian Kwan &#8211; A late season surge, fueled by a large trade, almost propelled Ian to the playoffs. How will he fare this year?</li>
<li>James Land &#8211; I was ok. Maybe I’ll be better this year?</li>
<li>Anthony Cudznovic &#8211; Was hurt by the loss of his first round draft pick, David Johnson. Hopefully his luck will improve this year.</li>
<li>Jaiden Gerig &#8211; Fournette and Crew led to the playoff berth for this fantasy football newcomer. Can he repeat last year&#8217;s success?</li>
<li>Reece Boyd &#8211; Renowned trader and semifinals team looks to climb even higher this year. Can he do it?</li>
<li>Siddharth Sharma &#8211; Last year’s third place finisher, and regular season best record. Sidd returns again to try to win it all.</li>
<li>Damian Larson &#8211; With the hopes that he will quit asking for everyone’s best player, our runner up returns to contend once again for the championship.</li>
<li>Thomas Huerta &#8211; Last year’s champion, and current trophy holder. Thomas will seek to dominate once again and repeat as champ.</li>
</ul>
<p>Those are the teams. We still need to figure out a draft date, but it seems the leading possibility is August 29th, starting at 6:00 pm (that&#8217;s a Wednesday, my dudes). Let me know what you guys think about that date and time.</p>
<p>Finally, I’m going to open up several spots this year for guest writers to contribute their write ups this year. By the end of the year last year I was experiencing write up fatigue, so what better way to relieve that fatigue than by pushing the job onto the rest of you! I’d like to fill five write up spots this year with volunteers. If you would like to sign up, let me know and I will give you a slot.</p>

b2
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/ff-writeup/index.php/2018/08/12/preseason/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

0

